Cheung Kin Wong

Full-stack Developer

Profile

As a Full-stack Developer, I specialize in crafting intuitive solutions that prioritize user satisfaction. I'm deeply passionate about harmonizing technology and design to deliver seamless and engaging user experiences. My expertise includes debugging, refining code, and continuous optimization to ensure a robust and reliable platform.

Education

VDAB Full-stack Developer (2024 - present)

- Fundamentals C# and .NET
- Test driven development TDD
- Software design pattern MVC
- Relational database MSSQL
- Creating a Web API
- Server side rendering RAZOR
- Scrum project

BeCode Front-end Developer (2019-2020)

• T2 Hackaton Hasselt

VDAB DTP-Prepress (2010-2011)

Chemistry AP Hoge School (2007-2009)

Experience

ZAPFLOOR Front-End Developer (2020 - 2024)

- Creating and maintaining user-, operator,- and mobile client
- Fetching and Consuming API
- Incorporating and managing translations
- Ensuring platform works across time zones
- Implementation of integrations for Authentication, Payment and Door access
- Creating and designing wire frames and mock-ups
- Leading meetings and providing presentations
- Writing documentation and peer Code reviewing
- Debugging and refactoring of the codebase
- Providing customer and tech support

Printing house Gazelle prepress Coordinator (2011 - 2019)

- Designing and layouting
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign

Umicore Lab technician (2007 - 2009)

Quality control and analytics

Contact info

- Alfred Oststraat 8 bus 4 2140 Borgerhout
- cheungkin.wong@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/cheungkin/
- **** 0485/47 41 48

Languages

Dutch - Native English - Fluent French - Intermediate Cantonese - Native Mandarin - Basic

Soft skills

Communication
Problem solving
Critical thinking
Growth mindset
Attention to detail

Technical skills

C# / .NET Vue.js / Nuxt.js Razor/Blazor React Material Design **MSSQL** HTML /CSS Web API **MVC** TS/JS Figma /Adobe XD TDD Git/GitHub OAuth /SSO NPM Stripe Mollie Heroku Agile /Jira **Paypal** SaltoKS

Hobbies



Cheung Kin Wong

Full-stack Developer

Profiel

Als Full-stack Developer specialiseer ik mij in het ontwikkelen van intuïtieve oplossingen die gericht zijn op gebruikerstevredenheid. Ik ben gepassioneerd door het samenbrengen van technologie en design om aantrekkelijke gebruikerservaringen te creëren. Mijn expertise omvat ook het debuggen, verfijnen van code en continue optimalisatie om een robuust en betrouwbaar platform te garanderen.

Opleiding

VDAB Full-stack Developer (2024 - nu)

- Fundamenten C# en .NET
- Test driven development TDD
- Software design pattern MVC
- Relational database MSSQL
- Maken van Web API
- Server side rendering RAZOR
- Scrum project

BeCode Front-end Developer (2019-2020)

• T2 Hackaton Hasselt

VDAB DTP-Prepress (2010-2011)

Chemie AP Hogeschool (2007-2009)

Ervaring

ZAPFLOOR Front-End Developer (2020 - 2024)

- Maken en onderhouden van user-, operator,- and mobile client
- Ophalen en consumtie van API
- Integratie en manage van vertalingen
- Implementatie van integraties voor Authenticatie, Betalingen en toegangsbeheer
- Maken en ontwerpen van wireframes en mockups
- Leiden van meetings
- Procedures documenteren en peer code review
- Debugging en refactoring van de codebase
- Klant en tech support

Drukkerij Gazelle prepress Coördinator (2011 - 2019)

- Ontwerp en opmaak
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign

Umicore Laborant (2007 - 2009)

• kwaliteitscontrole en analyse

Contact info

- Alfred Oststraat 8 bus 4 2140 Borgerhout
- cheungkin.wong@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/cheungkin/
- **** 0485/47 41 48

Talen

Nederlands - Moedertaal Engels - Vloeiend Frans - Goed Cantonees - Moedertaal Mandarijns - Basis

Soft skills

Communicatie
Probleemoplossend
Kritisch denken
Groeigericht
Oog voor detail

Technische skills

Vue.js /Nuxt.js C# / .NET
React Razor/Blazor
Material Design MSSQL
HTML /CSS Web API
TS/JS MVC
Figma /Adobe XD TDD

Git/GitHub OAuth /SSO
NPM Stripe

Heroku Mollie
Agile /Jira Paypal
SaltoKS

Hobby's

